In Japan, 99.9% of Criminal Trials End in a Guilty Verdict
Higuruma Law Office
The Morioka Mother-Child Murder Incident
Questionable Innocent Verdict.
"It Was Bought"
Former Judge Comments on Crooked Lawyer's Statements
The verdict was innocent.
Guess even murderers go free
if they can pay up.
How much did he dump on this...
The law is dead. Prosecutors are useless.
Refusing to Accept the Current Ruling,
They Have Appealed Seeking A Revision
Morioka Prosecutor's Office
I worked hard, too.
Appeal Trial (Second Trial)
Guilty. Life Sentence.
Culling Game Player
Higuruma Hiromi
Episode 55
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 2
Culling Game Player
Itadori Yuji
Amai Rin
Maybe so
Complete Book of the Six Codes
2: Players breaching the first rule
shall be stripped of their technique.
8:  Players who do not show a change in points
within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
Please have a seat.
Thank you for inviting me here.
Next Episode
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 3